<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pages on Digital Tea Room</title><link>https://digitaltearoom.com/pages/</link><description>Recent content in Pages on Digital Tea Room</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://digitaltearoom.com/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pumpkin Stuff for October</title><link>https://digitaltearoom.com/post/2020/pumking-stuff-for-october/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 13:20:06 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://digitaltearoom.com/post/2020/pumking-stuff-for-october/</guid><description>And now it is Autumn, or Fall if you are in the New Continent, but it is everywhere is pumpkin season. And it is my favorite Autumn&amp;rsquo;s fruit1 and I eat it in any way. And some time I make it for eating it with a good cup of tea.
So in this post I make a recipe for the &amp;ldquo;Witch&amp;rsquo;s Bread&amp;rdquo;, a family recipe for pumpkin tea cake. For start you need to have:</description></item><item><title>French Press</title><link>https://digitaltearoom.com/post/2020/french-press/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 13:52:32 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://digitaltearoom.com/post/2020/french-press/</guid><description>The other day I was searching for making tea without using teabag or other stuff. This happen because I don&amp;rsquo;t like cleaning them after making tea.
So, after some search, I find the french press.
The French press The french press is a &amp;ldquo;coffee&amp;rdquo; thing, where you put boiling water and the coffee and, after some time, press it so the coffee powder will stay down under the press and the coffee will stay over the press.</description></item><item><title>Experiment With Peach Tea</title><link>https://digitaltearoom.com/post/2020/experiment-with-peach-tea/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 09:35:14 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://digitaltearoom.com/post/2020/experiment-with-peach-tea/</guid><description>I love peach tea when is an hot day. But the ones you found in the shops are with sugars and other things like rose and I don&amp;rsquo;t want something like this. So I start with some experiment to make it home.
The tea I use a base black tea peach in bag because it is the easy way to find it and is not too expensive for make some experiment but you can use more expensive tea for your tea.</description></item><item><title>Ice Tea Without Heat</title><link>https://digitaltearoom.com/post/2020/ice-tea-without-heat/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 15:03:24 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://digitaltearoom.com/post/2020/ice-tea-without-heat/</guid><description>Welcome Summer, the hotter season of the year and the season wher I don&amp;rsquo;t like cocking or making tea. But I need drink tea for survive. I like drink tea when working, when I am tired, when I am reading&amp;hellip;
So I find a way to make tea without heat. And I don&amp;rsquo;t want to make hot tea, it&amp;rsquo;s summere, I want to make cold tea.
What you need This is a list of what I use and the ammount of tea I use.</description></item></channel></rss>